♪ Stick it up, mister! ♪
♪ Hear what I say, sir, yeah ♪
♪ Get your hands
in the air, sir! ♪
♪ Then you will get
no hurt, mister, no, no, no ♪
♪ I said, yeah
♪ What they say
♪ Don't you hear me say, yeah?
♪ Listen what they say
♪ Do you believe I would take
such a thing with me ♪
♪ And give it to a policeman?
I wouldn't do that ♪
♪ And if I do that,
I would say "Sir ♪
♪ "Come on
and put the charge on me" ♪
♪ I wouldn't do that, oh ♪
♪ I wouldn't do that ♪
♪ I'm not a fool
to hurt myself ♪
♪ So I was innocent
of what they done to me ♪
♪ They was wrong ♪
♪ They was wrong
♪ Give it to me one time  ♪
♪ Give it to me two times
♪ Give it to me three times
...
This is an abusive
work relationship.
Get into character.
My character's gonna murder
your character.
Ah... all right. All right.
Kinda diggin' these wheels
though, right? We could do this.
Get one of these bad boys, drive
across country, me and Cody.
- Someday, I hope.
- And how's he doin'?
You know, keep hoping
that time will do its thing,
but he keeps pulling away.
I had to take his car keys
from him this morning.
Did not go well.
- Idiot!
- Stop!
Yes, finish strong!
- I know him.
- I bring you lunch.
- So smooth.
- Thanks.
- Overcompensating?
- Constantly. Just for you.
- Wow!
What a mess!
Er... compliments
of Mama Padilla.
Ah...
I told her not
to make the heavy stuff
when you have a meet...
Just tell her I love them
and thank you very much.
- Hey...
- Hi y'all.
Hello, family. Ooh, cupcakes.
What mood was your dad in
this morning?
Shitty. He stole my car keys.
It's not like
I have another set though.
You just don't learn.
He's gonna kill you, white boy.
I'll be home before him.
But he did say
he'd be working late, so...
My mom seems torqued up.
I think something's
going down today.
My mom said
a little extra prayer.
She always does before a raid.
Now I'm going to be worried
about this all day.
Guys, they are gonna be fine.
- Yeah.
- All right, they always are.
♪ You can forget
all your troubles...
All right, there it is.
Let's do it.
Yep.
It's go time.
♪ Just take a walk
down this street  ♪
♪ Lots of people you will meet
...
Here we go.
- Hey...
- Hey, señor.
- Hey!
- No gas?
No gas.
- Sign says "gas".
- Lo siento, no gas today.
If you don't have any gas,
your sign should say "no gas".
Try down the road,
we're all out.
How far down the road?
I gotta use the bathroom.
- Piss on the road.
- I don't have to piss.
I've got a turtle that needs
to be released in the wild.
Know what I mean?
Hey, cabron.
- Easy.
- Better get back in.
I just had to use the bathroom.
That's all. Take it easy.
Gotcha. Nice job, Wash.
It's go time.
Ooh...
Ah man,
you put my favourite shirt on.
Just for you, Padilla.
- Home in time for dinner, right?
- Hell, yeah!
Hey guys.
Just in case, let's keep
our phones on vibrate, okay?
- Yeah.
- Sure.
Hey, have fun in
AP Calculus, nerd.
- Oh, you know I will.
- Must be nice.
- Free ride to Princeton.
- Bye.
Hey, you're the new girl, right?
Yeah, thanks for reminding me.
- I'm Cody.
- Teresa.
I think you're in my chem class,
we should like, study some time.
I'm actually kind of hoping
to pass that class. But thanks.
Nice... Strike out!
It wasn't a strike out
necessarily.
More like a... scouting report.
She don't know
what she's missing.
- I'll go on a date with you.
- All right.
Lower your weapon.
Grenade!
Move in.
Here!
- Clear.
All the way to Mexico,
huh, baby?
Deep and dirty, like your mom.
The DEA didn't get lucky.
There's a rat!
And Benito will get rid of it!
DEA!
Clear.
Stop!
Shit, it's wired.
It's wired. Go! Go back. Go!
Shit!
Move down to the left,
old man!
Go, go, go, go, go.
Move, move.
Come on!
Just move!
Go, go, go.
Everyone out!
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Aargh!
Shit, was tighter than a--
Sniper! Sniper.
Across the border!
Man down!
Manny.
Shoot. Shoot!
Go! Go! Come on!
Go!
Can Jesse Padilla
please come to the office?
What happened?
I didn't say bye
to him this morning.
I'm sorry.
Jesse...
I don't know what to do.
Damn it, Cody. Really?
Been texting you for hours.
What are you talking about?
I told you where I was going.
That's not the point.
This is not the night
to ghost me.
Jesus Christ, Dad.
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- What happened?
Nothing, I'm fine. Okay?
Except...
I've been worried sick
about you,
because you can't bother
to text?
I was focused on Jesse, okay?
He's a wreck.
It's just not safe right now.
We can't keep doing this. Okay?
I'm 18 now. You gotta loosen
the leash a little bit.
I just need you
to be more careful.
- If I text, you text me back.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
I should have texted you back.
Look...
I know it's gonna be hard,
but I was talking
with the other parents.
We don't think you guys
should hang out for a while.
- Are you serious?
- Just for a while.
We get the drill.
There's other people around,
we don't say anything.
You know, right now
it's just a risk. Okay?
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
Come on.
Let me make something to eat.
I already ate.
Manny was the best of us.
A man who cared deeply
about his community...
his friends...
Most of all, his family.
A loving husband
to his wife, Lucy.
I'm so proud of his son, Jesse.
He was our North Star
and we always tried
to follow his example.
It seems
that we have a very big problem.
In this house.
And it seems
we have an infestation...
Rats. Rats. Rats.
A rat told the DEA
...about our tunnel.
And they stole our cheese.
So where's our cheese, huh?
Where's our cheese?
Vasquez killed a pig for me.
So he's clean.
But all you idiots...
How many rats are there here?
Who's the rat, cabrones?
Was it you, my friend?
Are you the rat?
No, boss. No, never.
Kill him.
I know he's your cousin.
I gave you your first job
together, remember?
When you were kids.
No, cousin, don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
If we find the rats,
they'll lead us to the pigs!
Rats and pigs, really?
Quite a performance.
You feel better now?
-  He's improved, no?
-  No, he hasn't.
This is no way to live.
He's survived much worse.
You shouldn't even be here.
Looks like you need the help.
You're helping in El Paso.
You lost an entire tunnel.
Months of work for nothing.
What do you think he'd do?
Flush out the rats.
Like I'm doing.
Papito operated like a shadow.
The work
you're doing there is vital.
I can only trust you.
Let's get started. We are
having a lab session today.
So everyone, please find
a partner. Don't be shy.
-  Me?
- Mm-hm.
When I was little, I used
to blow shit up all the time.
I'm not sure
that's the assignment.
The 13 x 100, the smaller one.
Oh, you actually know this?
That wasn't a bullshit?
That was mostly bullshit,
but like I said,
when I was younger,
I was like a mad scientist.
- I was a real punk.
- Was?!
How do you like El Paso so far?
Pretty cool, right?
- Please tell me you're kidding.
- Of course.
I am trying to like it.
I mean, I kind of have to.
It's not like we can move back.
I had a whole life
in San Antonio.
All my friends are there.
But now I have to start over.
That's gotta be tough.
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
At least I have a lab partner.
- Shall we?
- Yeah.
- Cheers!
- Ready?
Yep.
Whoa! Jeez!
Boom... science.
He's clean.
Hi, I'm here
to collect the order. Thanks.
Benito knows it's me.
If he knew it was you,
you wouldn't be here.
I can't do this.
I can't help you anymore.
I'm out. I'm sorry.
Then you're out.
That was the deal.
Just give me a few days
to work out witness protection.
- Thank you.
- Any word on the new tunnel?
Not yet.
I heard Benito's sister
lives in El Paso.
- I didn't know he had a sister.
- I think her name's Natalia.
I bet she's here
under a fake name.
- You know what she's doing here?
- Don't know.
Everything about her,
they keep real quiet.
- Appreciate it, thanks.
- Thanks.
Come on, gentlemen!
Hey, what's going on?
We're not supposed to hang out.
Er, I am moving
and I have to transfer schools.
What? Like moving away?
We're moving in
with my mum's sister in Abilene,
eight hours away.
It's either that or Spain.
I have grandparents there.
- Oh, man.
- Yeah.
The DEA's death benefits
are, um, shit,
as it turns out,
and with my dad not here,
we can't afford
to stay in the house.
Mom's medical
is gonna run out soon.
I don't think I can talk
about that right now.
- It's okay.
- Hey, come here. It's okay.
...the news
from El Paso and Juárez.
Did you hear Jesse and
his mom are having to move away?
Yeah, I heard.
We'll visit. Roadtrip.
Isn't there anything
the DEA can do to help them?
What about all that cash
you seized in the raid?
It goes
into our operating budget.
That's how we keep pace
with the cartels.
But Jesse's dad died
getting that money.
Doesn't the DEA
owe the family something?
Yeah, I hear you, bud,
but it's not the way it works.
We're setting up a GoFundMe
for them. We'll do what we can.
So if you die, I get a GoFundMe?
- To Manny.
- Manny.
I always wished
I could be more like Manny.
Really?
He wanted to be like you.
- No.
- Yeah.
I don't mean about the job.
Manny was such a great father.
Hey, man. You're a great father.
No, Wendy was the one who
knew how to be there for Cody.
Even after she got sick,
she held us together...
right up till the end.
And now...
Yeah.
I don't know shit, right?
I mean, I don't have kids...
Lizzy's been bringing Deni
on the training exercises.
Yeah, yeah...
She wants Deni to join up.
I don't want Cody
anywhere near this job.
Way too cowboy, that kid.
He'll get himself killed.
I know, I hear that, but...
It looks like she's trying to
spend some time with her, right?
No pressure, no agenda.
Things open up.
Wrist control. Grab the wrist.
If they're backing away
from you, go double wrist.
Put your weight on them.
Trip them.
There it is.
Another way,
same wrist control, underhook.
Scoot under and drag 'em back.
There it is.
- Hey.
- Cody wrestles, right?
- Yeah.
You want to get him out here.
Throw him around a bit.
- I just want him watching today.
- All right.
Come on, guys.
Let's get on these bags.
♪ Whatever happened
to the plans we made ♪
♪ Laying awake after midnight ♪
♪ Oh, I don't want
to lose that flame...
Hey. Cody's with me.
-  Cody, what's the word?
- Hey Wash. I'm good.
Ray, I just rolled up on
a trap house on the south side.
- Wanna check it out?
- Is it locked down?
Cops have been here for hours.
Nothing to worry about.
What do you say?
Want to see a trap house?
Yeah, that'll be cool.
♪ The years go by and somehow
I just can't forget...
There it is.
All right...
- How's it going, Cody?
- Hey. All right.
- Hey.
- How did they bust it?
- It was a tough case.
Tweaker passed out
on the sidewalk.
Nobody bothered to bring him in.
A black-and-white
was just rolling by.
- Good help's hard to find.
- Yeah.
Welcome to the glamorous life
of dealing drugs.
- I'd say don't touch anything...
- Yeah, no danger of that.
- Anybody talking?
- Nah.
Good soldiers,
nothing on the wiretaps either
but I think there must be
a distribution hub nearby.
Yeah, that'll make sense.
- Wash... Reynolds.
- Yeah.
His sister, Natalia.
PFM has heard the rumour too,
but they got nothing on her.
No files, no photos. Nothing.
Her father could've wiped
her records decades ago.
It's gotta be how
she's getting back and forth.
If she is in El Paso,
she probably has a US passport,
solid identity, all backstopped.
So we're not gonna find her.
Not unless she wants us to.
All right. Let's go.
Cody, a couple more minutes
and we're out of here.
It's all good.
Let's clarify the crazy
coming out of your mouth.
You want us
to jack a drug cartel?
No. A trap house
owned by a cartel.
I was just
at one of these places.
I'm telling you,
it's amateur hour.
One lookout, one dealer,
bottom of the barrel dumbasses.
A couple of junkies sleeping
in the corner. That's it.
Maybe with the money
that we steal from him,
Jesse and his mom
can buy a house,
- pay off her medical bill.
- Jesse can go to college.
I just want to know
what my job is.
Kyle, you would have
a really important job.
- Lay it on me.
- The lookout.
Okay, I'm the lookout.
Are we doing this for real
or are we just bullshitting?
Deni, I don't love
how quiet you're being.
I'm thinking about it.
Between us,
we got it all covered.
I'd be the getaway driver.
And Deni, your mom takes you
to training exercises.
So you know the basics.
Even better, you know
where all the DEA offsites are.
- So...
- You borrow your mum's keys
and then boom,
we have access
to top of the line
DEA equipment.
All compliance gear only,
non-lethal, no one gets hurt.
Look, even if we could rob
a trap house, then what?
We can't just FedEx Jesse
a box full of drug money.
You have to set up
offshore shell companies
with a pristine laptop
and open a ton of bank accounts,
but only with small deposits
to make sure you stay under
the IRS reporting requirements.
Your dad worked
money laundering, right?
- Ah, shit.
- So we're covered.
Is this gonna be like
the outdoor survival club
you tried to start?
I'm being serious. These
assholes killed Jesse's dad.
If one of our parents got killed
and we asked Jesse
to help us out, he'd say yes.
You know he would.
I'm not saying let's do it,
but it does sound
pretty righteous.
Doing this would be a huge risk,
for sure.
We've all been saying that
we want to help Jesse, right?
So this is how.
The DEA should be taking care
of them and they're not.
So we will. We can do this,
but it has to be all of us.
He's clear.
Hi. I'm here for the order.
You're all set. So walk away,
enjoy your new life.
Thank you.
A vehicle on the shoulder.
Gun!
Everyone on the floor.
Down on the floor, flat!
Shit!
Hit the pedal!
Get down! Get down!!
Ray! Ray, Ray, Ray,
come on. That's it.
Get down.
Hey, look at you,
buddy. You're a lucky man.
You're lucky, hombre.
Looks pretty good on you.
Natalia Cabrera,
tell us about her.
Okay, we get it. A lot of people
don't like talking to us.
They've got families
they want to protect.
You don't have any family.
You were recruited
out of the orphanage.
You got options.
You killed a DEA agent in Texas.
Even if
we can't make that stick,
we got you on the informant.
People are gonna be lining up
to get on the jury
to put you in the chair.
The only way you survive this
is by talking to us.
Natalia Cabrera.
We know she's in El Paso.
What's she doing here?
Well, shit, I'll tell you,
cerdos, free of charge.
Natalia Cabrera
is in El Paso for you.
She's here
to crack the cover identities
of all you DEA agents.
She's digging.
She's spreading money around.
They're gonna find you
and wipe you out
and all of your families.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, kid.
Look, something came up.
I'm gonna be at work late.
- Okay, cool. Good to know.
- Did you have a good day?
Ah, it's been fine.
Nothing special.
- Don't stay out too late.
- Okay.
- We still need to be careful.
- Okay, cool.
- Bye.
- See ya. Bye.
Jesus, he's gotta take
a leak sometime.
Why'd you say that?
Now I have to take a leak.
- Me too.
- Me three.
You all got bladder problems.
How long do you guys
want to wait?
I have an essay
due first period.
You should do your homework
early on crime night.
- Not getting cold feet, Yvonne?
- Absolutely.
Again, this will
fire a cartridge.
If you miss,
this end still works as a taser.
- I got it, I got it.
- What is your job?
I sit in the car like a loser
while you guys
do all the cool shit.
If things get messed up,
I call 911.
I don't wanna go to jail
'cause you lost your shit.
I don't lose my shit.
I'm ice cold.
We can't go to jail.
We're still minors.
Yeah, but I'm not.
Worst case, us three will do
a little time in juvey.
When we turn 18,
it all goes away.
Cody will take the fall.
It was his idea.
Thanks.
Guys, we don't have guns
but they probably definitely do.
Maybe I should wear
a flak jacket too?
Hey, we're on. We're doing this?
- Shit.
- Yes.
- Have fun without me.
- You want to trade?
- No, bye. Get out.
- You want go?
Okay.
- For Jesse.
- Yeah, for Jesse.
Okay, same plan. Zerg rush,
knock over the candle,
take the cash, out.
-  What do we do?
- Don't know.
That way. Go.
Shit.
Oh, shit.
Oh, Jesus.
I can't see! I can't see!
- Okay. Get the money!
-  Let's go.
What's going on?
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
It's Cabrera's money!
You're making a big mistake!
-  Go!
-  Follow me.
Oh, shit.
Shit!
Cody, clear!
- It's us!
- I knew you'd be okay.
- I didn't call the cops!
- Good job!
- Oh my God, that was insane!
- Shit.
You guys okay?
Let's go!
- How are the eyes?
- Better. Coming back.
We have a grand total.
Wanna hear it?
- Yeah.
- All in, we have $497.
- Huh...
- Mm-hm.
Oh my God.
I don't think we're sending
Jesse to Yale with that.
We're the biggest morons
on the planet.
We almost got ourselves killed
for not even 500 bucks.
Our obituaries would be so sad.
"Local teens executed. Should
have got an after-school job."
- You know what? I'm proud of us.
- Really?
- For real.
- Yeah?
We did the thing
and when it all went to shit,
nobody panicked,
we stuck together
and helped each other out.
- That was a goddamn rush.
- Hell, yeah.
Calm down.
There's no reason to panic.
Vasquez will keep his mouth
shut. He'll do time. Besides...
It was just a trap house.
There was barely any money.
It's not about the money.
This makes us look weak!
First the tunnel, then this!
Open season on us.
We cannot flinch.
This happened
in your city, didn't it?
Find out who it was
and make an example out of 'em?
The squatter said the trap house
got knocked over last night.
That was just a smash and grab.
These bodies happened later.
Yeah,
Benito's not the forgiving type.
We found a helmet
with night vision.
These bastards aren't civilians.
Military grade. Very strange.
No, it's not
strange. It was the DEA.
They're going rogue.
They lost their informant,
their friend,
and they're out for revenge,
that's it.
Who'd be dumb enough
to steal from them anyway?
I doubt they know
who it belonged to.
- Was probably just a one-off.
- I hope so. For their sake.
- Ow! My tongue.
- Let me get that.
Oh! No, it's fine. I got it.
To be honest,
I'm a little nervous.
Oh, I... I was nervous
because I thought you weren't.
- So...
- Oh, yeah.
...
Sorry,
this crazy woman's my mom.
Oh no, I... trust me,
I get that.
- Yeah, your mom too?
- Uh, no, my dad.
My mom passed away
actually, so...
- God, I'm sorry.
- Oh, no, no. I appreciate it.
It was three years ago.
Leukaemia, so...
What about you and your folks?
Still together or...?
Divorced. Dad's somewhere.
He had a kid and decided,
it's not really my thing.
Ask me, an overprotective father
kind of sounds nice.
So, what's his deal?
He's always been about his job.
He's in construction,
project manager.
But now that it's just him,
he's gotta be the parent.
Like, who's gonna
keep me alive anyway.
Sorry? Keep you alive?!
What are you doing
on the weekends?
Like he owes that to my mom.
It's just another job
he's gotta do.
Sounds like
we have awesome families.
Maybe that's why
we're good lab partners.
I'm gonna give myself a mission.
I'm gonna make you happy
you moved here.
I'm gonna make you
love El Paso.
- Yeah.
- Boy likes a challenge.
Yeah, no, we're just...
We're getting filled in.
- How is your mom doing, Jesse?
- Uh, she's all right.
Um, she's just,
you know, job hunting,
which has been
kind of difficult...
Jesus! All right, would you
piss ants please shut up.
Hey, I'm on the phone! Stop it!
I'm gonna step outside
and deal with that.
- Can I call you guys back?
- Yeah, of course!
Thank you!
I'm never having kids.
Poor Jesse.
We didn't get what
we need from the trap house.
That's fine. Rookie mistake.
Won't happen again.
Right, because we're not robbing
any more trap houses.
Next we're gonna be hitting
one of Cabrera's money mules.
- So what now?
- The mule that collects cash
from the dealers. Spreads it
around cash businesses
controlled by the cartels
to clean it.
- I love it.
- Yeah.
- Cody!
- I'm serious.
This is our mule. They call him
El Viejo Malhumorado.
-  Grumpy old man.
- He looks like a hobo.
- Hm.
- He's kind of hot.
The idea is
to keep a low profile.
Every week he does
the same circuit around El Paso.
Laundromats, pawn shops, bars.
His van has to be filled
with cash.
- What's filled?
- Half a million. At least.
That's Jesse and his mom
well taken care of.
So, what do we think?
- I'm in...
-  Yes.
If we don't pull
the entire thing out of our ass.
This time
we actually have a plan.
El Viejo does
the same route every week?
-  Yep.
-  Great.
Then we have time
to really think this through.
If we do it smart this time,
then I'm in too.
- Then smart it is.
- Letting y'all know I'm also in.
Obviously.
So, where do we start?
I know where our parents
would start. Recon.
A shit ton of recon.
El Viejo is always
followed by two armed guards
in a sedan.
No way we just walk up
and taser those guys.
You're right. For them
we need some heavy artillery.
- Beanbag shotguns.
- They're non-lethal.
They just knock you
down for a while.
Beanbag shotguns.
I could handle one of those.
Kyle, I don't know. Deni and I
grew up hunting. You didn't.
I always beat your ass
at Fortnite. So I'm the master.
If they're up on it, why doesn't
the DEA just shut him down?
He's not the prize for them.
They're just
gathering intel for now.
They put a GPS
on his van, see where he goes,
- who he talks to.
-  So we do the same.
We'll make sure
our parents aren't following.
♪ ...an evacuation zone and
I think I need to operate now ♪
♪ And if all goes well
I'll return to the world...
This is where we do it.
The neighbourhood
should be empty
so there should be no traffic.
It'll be easy
to get in and out of there fast.
What about the customers?
We don't want anyone
to see what's happening.
- Kyle, that's your job.
- Kyle gets a job?
- I'm a part of this!
- Yeah, he's a part of this.
On the day, let's leave
our phones at school.
Keep our location history clean.
When we get El Viejo's van,
where the hell do we put it?
My grandpa's place.
It's out of town.
There's an old barn.
It's perfect.
Let's go!
-  Let her go!
-  I said drop it!
Okay.
Shit. No, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on.
Shit.
I got the keys!
I got her! Take this.
-  Come on. Let's go.
-  Let's get out of here!
-  Fuck you!
-  Yoo-hoo.
Suck on my bag, biatch!
Fortnite, I told you!
Yeah, nice one!
Come on, let's go.
Go, go, go, go!
Oh, good job, Kyle.
Holy shit! Did you see
that? Is your head okay, Deni?
Yeah. Are you okay?
Yeah, he's much better looking
in person.
- Bingo!
- Whoa!
He's still on us!
This isn't over yet!
If this ends in a police chase,
we're screwed,
so keep your masks on!
Doors!
Move, I got this.
I got you all back!
-  Shit! Sorry!
-  It's okay! Doors open!
Now!
I've got you,
you old son of a bitch.
Woo!
Fortnite!
Oh my God! That was insane.
- Wow, did you see that?
-  Wait. Get a selfie.
♪ That's right! ♪
♪ I got a little funny doggy ♪
♪ Set your name
straight right off ♪
♪ Oooooo ♪
♪ Woohoo ♪
♪ I know a disco kitten
named Minnie ♪
♪ She'll put a new smile
on your necktie, that's right...
Yeah, I gotta go.
Hey, hey El Viejo. We got him.
Yeah? Please tell me
his head's still attached.
We caught a break this time.
He just walked
into a field office.
Smart man.
He knows Benito's gonna kill him
for losing that shipment.
- He want witness protection?
- What do you think?
I'll see what he's got.
-  So it was a crew?
- Yes, there were four of them.
- Two women and two men.
- You get a look at them?
No, they used tear gas on us.
They all had gas masks on.
I couldn't see.
- Cartel?
- Oh, God. No. God, no.
I wouldn't be here
if it was them.
This was sloppy, not pros.
You could tell there was...
They did get to jump on us.
But the two guards with me,
I can tell you all about them.
Oh, come on. Those guys
are long gone, you know that.
Come on, give us something
that goes up the chain.
I... I handled my end only--
What do you know
about Natalia Cabrera?
- Well, I've heard the name.
- Any idea what she looks like?
- No, I--.
- Come on, brother.
You want WITSEC, you're gonna
have to do better than that.
I can't give you Benito
and his top guys, all right?
I can tell you more about
how they move things around.
I can tell you about the beer
truck. That's something.
Who the hell is doing this?!
How come you haven't found them?
Tell me!
Our whole network is burnt.
I have to start
everything from scratch.
I'll find them!
It's the DEA pigs.
They're making fun of us!
I'm sure they're laughing at us.
I'm sure it's them!
The DEA
doesn't operate that way.
Oh yeah? Then what?!
- Don't be paranoid.
- I want...
I want the DEA names,
you have to prove it to me.
I want their names.
I want their faces.
I want their addresses.
I want them dead...
I want their wives
and kids dead. Their pets too!
Set a trap!
- Teresa.
- I've got to get to class.
I'm sorry
I haven't been around, for real.
It's just wrestling
has been insane.
It's fine,
I just don't need this.
I want to make it up to you.
So how about go hiking with me.
I know a great spot,
it'll be epic.
- I don't know.
- Look, if you don't go then...
I'll be too devastated to study,
and then we'll both fail chem.
- This is extortion.
- It's actually blackmail.
Okay.
- Wow!
- Yeah, I know.
My mom used to take me here.
She loved the mountains.
What was she like?
She was really gentle.
She'd always joke
that she couldn't wait
to become a little old lady.
She still had
the whole mama bear thing going,
so you wouldn't want
to mess with her.
Was it a good marriage?
Were they at least happy?
Yeah, they were.
I couldn't tell you how though,
because my dad is so massively
closed off and she was so there.
I miss her a lot.
♪ You know I came here
to leave you ♪
♪ And it was so sad
we could only laugh ♪
♪ I held your hand
like it was all I had ♪
♪ Out of the blue
Ooh, ooh...
Are you gonna go back
to ignoring me after this?
- What? No.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
- Okay.
I like you a lot.
I like you too.
♪ As we were reaching
for the door ♪
♪ I loved you deeper
than I ever had before ♪
♪ Oh, the richest of blue ♪
♪ Knowing I can't leave
without you ♪
What do you guys think?
Second time
the Cabreras have been hit.
- No way this is random.
- I'm with Ellie.
This could be a rival cartel.
We took out the tunnel.
Cabrera's are vulnerable.
Somebody's making a move.
Really think this is cartel?
I'd expect it
to be a lot bloodier.
We're not hearing anything
on the wiretaps
- about another cartel.
- Maybe it's an inside job.
Some mid-level players
see things go wobbly,
decide they're gonna grab
some for themselves.
Same problem. Where's the blood?
I've never seen
a sicario use a beanbag round.
Okay, one other possibility.
Both places that got hit were
places that we were up on.
You thinking an inside job?
We were up in a lot of places,
didn't mean anything.
Think about this. In the middle
of robbing El Viejo,
the thieves take the time
to take our GPS tracker off.
- Like they knew it was there.
- Yeah.
Or they were smart enough
to check
for trackers
on a cartel vehicle.
- I'd check.
- So it was you?
Yeah, it was me.
I robbed El Viejo.
You know
who uses beanbag rounds?
Law enforcement.
You know who else? Nobody.
Yeah, well,
it can't be one of us.
Nobody'd be crazy enough
to pull that shit.
Okay, so maybe it's not
one of us but it's a big office.
Look around.
Yeah... okay.
From now on,
everything's on lockdown.
Any information on the Cabreras
stays close hold.
Yep.
We got something
off the wiretaps.
Talk about a new tunnel.
We got a location.
SMILE!
Masks up! Masks up!!
They knew we were up
on that phone.
Yeah, you're right.
We got a problem.
Shit!
Goddamn!
Wow, look at this place.
Nice work.
Papito will be proud of you.
That's all I need.
How soon
until we're operational?
Beer truck arrives on Tuesday.
Mm-hm. Yeah, I know.
Look.
Surprise! Look at this.
Picture of the day.
Oh, look at this guy.
Look, how handsome!
-  Hey...
- Hey.
Hey... I need
to give you a curfew.
What? Why? What did I do?
It's not you. I can't have you
out late right now.
So from now on,
be home by 9:00, okay?
Come on... that's bullshit.
- Cody, don't start.
- If the cartel's gonna whack us,
I'm pretty sure they can do it
during business hours.
What is your game plan here?
Work till one of us is dead?
You're gonna lock me in my room
so you can fight your war
on drugs?
By the way, drugs have won.
I'm 18. You can't control me.
- Cody...
- What are you gonna do?
Cody!
Yeah, no. Lucy, no, of course.
You're so welcome.
It really wasn't even
that much money.
Can you say that again?
Wow. No, that's great.
You know how much we all care
about you? Say hi to Jesse.
That was, uh, Lucy Padilla.
She called to thank everybody
for the money.
Apparently, there was about
80 grand in the GoFundMe.
In the last couple of weeks,
it's gone up to 300 grand.
- Uh, that's...
- Yeah...
Wash, get me a list of all
the staffers who were read in.
Sit 'em down and ask for alibis.
They're gonna be pissed,
- but let's do it.
- Yep, on it.
All right, it must have
gone viral or something
because we are getting
like a ton of donations.
Oh... there's Cody.
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
- Tell him the good news.
- Yeah, okay.
So that GoFundMe, it's at six
figures and it's still going.
What?! That's... I'm so happy
to hear that, man. That's great.
It's a miracle, man,
like straight up.
We might be able to buy a house
and move back to El Paso,
which would be incredible.
God, a house.
I love that for you guys.
- Oh, we gotta go.
- Cool, bye.
- Oh, if only he knew.
- I got plans for the next one.
- Say what now?
- I have good intel from my dad.
- We can't quit now.
- We already quit.
While we're ahead.
That's when you quit.
We get a little something
for us this time.
You're almost 18.
We could go as far away
from El Paso as we want.
We could go to school,
start a business, travel.
- Easy, man.
- Kyle, come on. What do you say?
- Um...
- One more time?
I don't know,
maybe if everyone else is, sure.
- No, well everybody isn't.
- Yeah, and Jesse's good.
We're done, we can chill now.
This isn't us.
You do know that our parents
don't give a shit about us.
They could get shot tomorrow,
we'd have nothing.
I'll speak for myself,
I'd have had nothing.
I'm already down one parent.
So is Jesse.
Screw the cartel and the DEA.
We hit the slash truck,
we are free from all of it.
Look, man, I don't know
if you're on your period or...
but...
Deni, are you okay?
-  Oh my God, Deni.
-  Crap. Oh, shit.
- Deni?
-  Deni, you okay?
- Whoa... Deni...
-  Lie down, lie down.
Want some water?
Deni?
Hey... Hey, baby.
Deni, hey. Hey.
How long does the sedative last?
She'll come around soon.
- Hey. You okay?
- Yep.
- Yeah?
- How is she?
They're gonna run
some more tests,
but it's a concussion.
Delayed onset, they said,
but I think she fell down
some stairs last week.
She was fine until today.
I'm glad you were there.
It could have been a lot worse.
Yeah.
I just came to drop Lizzy off,
but I gotta get back to work.
- Okay, I'll see you at home.
- Bye.
- Hey, Cody...
- Yeah.
When did you say
Deni fell down the stairs?
I'm not sure. I wasn't there.
I think last week sometime.
- Okay.
- Yeah. See you.
Your mom said I could see you,
if you want to see me.
How you feeling?
Oh, so wiped.
I'm sorry. I was being
a total asshole and...
You didn't give me a concussion,
but agree on the asshole part.
Is there anything I can do?
I want to make it up to you.
Stay here a while.
Well, thanks for being here.
I know you don't like hospitals.
It's all good.
What's going on with you, Cody?
My dad...
Same shit.
I'd rather not talk about it.
That's too bad because I want
to talk about it. So...
Your dad is a protector type.
Classic dude.
And when your mom got sick,
he couldn't do shit about it.
He couldn't save her.
Nobody could.
All he could do
was watch it happen.
Now it's just him and you
and he is terrified
of losing
the last person he's got.
Terrified.
So if he keeps you
on a short leash,
that's not 'cause he thinks
you're weak or a little kid.
It's that he loves you.
Your dad loves you, Cody.
That's how he shows it, because
he doesn't know any other way.
Oh my God, I'm so glad
she's okay. Say hi for me.
Yeah, I will.
Not to freak you out,
but my mom's old-fashioned.
Uh-oh.
No, no. Nothing bad.
It's just she wants to meet you.
Would you mind coming for dinner
maybe on Thursday?
I'd be very grateful.
Oh, when you put it like that.
Shut up! See you on Thursday.
Beer truck will gas up.
We'll hit it right there.
I don't know. It's only
scheduled to stop this one time
and you know that truck stop's
gonna be all lit up.
If there was a way to do it,
you know I'm down. It's just...
I don't see it.
All right, guys.
I cannot stress this enough.
Details of this operation
do not leave this room.
All right, the beer truck
is gonna refuel here.
This truck stop on Highway 62
just after dark. Right?
After it fuels up, it's gonna be
on this empty stretch of highway
and that's where
we're gonna grab it.
Hey, I'm sorry, but something
came up. I can't make Thursday.
Don't be a dick.
You can't cancel on my mother.
- I'll make it up to you.
- I don't think so.
Friday... You and your mom,
you come over here.
My dad and I will happily make
dinner for you. So is that cool?
Actually...
Yes. That would be really sweet.
My mom would like that.
- Okay, great.
- You're still a dick though.
Total dick.
-  Hey.
- Hey.
Can I,
uh, ask you about something?
Yeah. Sure. What's up?
I didn't want to tell you
at first and I should have.
I'm seeing a girl at school.
She invited me
to have dinner with her mom.
And, of course, I said yes,
but then I had to cancel, so...
Why'd you cancel?
You know,
wrestling practice and all that.
I also promised Deni
that I'd visit her.
Um, and I kind of told her
that her and her mom could come
over this Friday for dinner.
I'm sorry. I know I should have
checked in with you, but--
- You need me to bail out?
- Yeah.
Bro' code, right? Okay.
- Awesome--
- Hey.
Did you hear anything about
the GoFundMe for Lucy and Jesse?
Yeah, no, yeah.
Jesse called me
and apparently, like it blew up
on TikTok or something.
It's... it's crazy. Yeah.
Thank God for TikTok,
whatever that is.
Just kidding.
I'll be home late tomorrow,
but you be home by 9:00.
- Of course.
-  See you.
See you.
It'll work. I'm positive.
- What if the forecast is wrong?
- Then we'll bail.
Okay, I'm bailing.
I've already bailed.
Fine. Me and Kyle
can do this on our own.
- You're gonna get killed!
- We got this.
The forecast is right.
The wind is kicking up good.
Let's go.
In position.
Keep your eyes
on the beer truck.
It looks like
they got an escort.
Copy that. See the beer truck.
One follow vehicle,
three inside.
Let's go!
- All right.
- Ready? Let's do this.
Okay.
All right. Now!
What the hell?
- Ray, what are we doing?
- Wash, hold your position.
Albright, Matthews,
let's take 'em there.
Copy that. Let's go.
Don't let them
get back out on the road.
Let's go!
Shit! No keys! Crap!
Check his pockets!
Here they are!
DEA, everyone on the ground!
DEA, get down.
- Oh, shit!
- Kyle, let's move.
DEA!
Get down. Get down!
Shit, that's my mom!
DEA, on the ground!
Drop your weapon!
-  Kyle, come on.
- Okay, okay.
Let's go, let's go!
Wash,
beer truck heading your way.
- I'm on it. I'll take it out.
- Stand down. Stand down.
I'm on it!
I just wanna go home. I'm sorry.
This isn't what I signed up for!
- We're good, we're good!
- No, we're not!
Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit.
I got this!
What the hell?!
Wash, stand down.
Cody, slow down!
Stand down! That's an order!
Goddammit!
- You okay?
- No! I'm not okay, Cody!
I'm sorry. Okay, I'm sorry.
I just wanna go home, bro'.
I wanna go home.
Hey... hey! What was that?
What's going on?
- Get a look at them?
- I could have followed them!
Ray, I know what's going on!
Padilla, wasn't your fault.
It wasn't mine, okay?
It happened.
And he'd want us to keep going.
He'd want to keep taking risks.
To do our jobs.
Yeah, I know.
I know you're right. Thanks.
Oh my God.
What did you do?
I know.
That got way out of hand.
- You think?
- Yvonne, our parents were there.
What? Are they okay?
Yeah, they're fine.
That was a mess.
They're not cold.
- No way.
- Where's the cash?
Oh, God.
Cody, stop!
Stop! There's no cash!
This is worth, I don't know...
A million. Tens of millions!
The money we stole
from the cartel was nothing!
They're gonna be
looking for it!
I know!
What if there's
a tracking beacon in there?
- There's not!
- How do you know?
Because we'd already be dead!
Yvonne told me.
Goddamn it, Cody!
Everything's gonna be fine.
We're cleaning it up now.
We should have quit
after El Viejo.
This is over, Cody.
It has to be.
Yeah, it's definitely over.
Hey. So I sat down with everyone
who was read in on the Cabreras.
They all had alibis
for all the heists.
Yeah, good. Yep.
That doesn't mean they couldn't
have passed the intel on.
To friends or family, even.
Yeah, they could've.
A lot of possibilities.
Yeah.
Well, if we don't get 'em,
the cartel will, right?
And they don't forget.
Cody, come out here.
Jesus, I thought you forgot.
Oh, dammit.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Hi!
Hi, uh, please come in.
You look great.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, Dad, Teresa. Teresa, Dad.
Hi.
Mr Seale,
it's really nice to meet you.
- Yeah, likewise. Call me Ray.
- Ray, this is my mother.
- Hi Ray.
- How are you?
- Call me Lydia.
- Lydia...
- Cody, nice to finally meet you.
- Yeah.
Teresa talks about you
all the time.
- Right?
- Mom...
All right... come on in.
See, I already embarrassed her.
Well, that's what parents
are for, right?
We were mostly commercial,
but now we're focusing
on residential.
It's like everyone's moving
to Texas.
Yeah, exactly.
- That's where all the money is.
- You okay?
Yeah.
Um... excuse me,
uh, where's your restroom?
Down the hallway,
second door to the right.
Gotcha.
Did you cook?
This is delicious.
Thank you.
- Oh man, seven hours.
- Seven hours.
- Yeah, about seven hours.
- Oh wow, that's a long time.
Yeah. Used to go up there
fishing all the time.
Being a single parent
is tough, right?
How have you managed it?
I had to let go
of the idea of perfect.
Perfect went out the door
along with her dad.
I've settled for the best I can.
Looks like you're doing
a great job with him.
Uh... Yeah, I mean, I hope so.
No one ever tells you if you're
being a bad parent, you know?
Yeah, figure it out on your own.
Cody's a good kid.
Got a great heart.
Just makes
bad decisions sometimes.
Sorry, I'm not trying to scare
your daughter off or anything.
Don't worry. No chance of that.
Yeah.
Family's hard.
Oh, trust me, I know.
Yeah.
What's the saying?
You choose your friends...
- But not your family.
- Yeah.
- Right, cheers to that.
- Salud.
- Thank you so much.
- Thanks for coming.
- Pleasure. Pleasure.
- Bye, Cody.
- Is everything okay?
- Let's get out of town tomorrow.
Go fishing. We haven't done
that in a long time.
Give us a chance to talk.
All right.
Good job.
They'll lead us
to the whole DEA team.
What?
Hey, what's up?
Hey, Cody.
Thanks for dinner tonight.
Teresa?!
I did enjoy getting to know you.
You won't believe me after this,
but it's true.
Now we want our beer truck back
with everything inside of it.
- Where's Deni?
- It's important you stay calm.
- It's important for Deni.
- Let me talk to her.
Okay.
Cody, don't come over here!
Okay, just... just tell me
what you want.
I'm gonna send you a location.
Be here with our beer truck
within two hours or Deni dies.
Daddy shows up, Deni dies too.
Are you clear?
- Yes.
- Guess I'll see you soon.
Cody! Get down!
Wash, I'm under attack.
My cover's blown. Call everyone.
Shit.
Hey, everyone okay?
Albright and Reynolds are fine.
They're at the office now
- locking it down.
- Thank God.
Listen, you said Cody was
visiting Deni at the hospital,
I'm here now,
and she's not in her room.
Matthews is freaking out.
Run a trace on Cody's phone.
Get his current location.
And run ID checks
on Lydia and Teresa Flores.
Okay. Listen, everything's
going to be fine. Okay?
Lydia Flores... EPPD just got
to her house. It's been torched.
No sign of her or the daughter.
Run silent.
Approach the extraction
with extreme caution.
Watch your crossfire
and watch your backdrop.
Don't shoot, I have a bomb
in here. Don't shoot!
Don't shoot, don't shoot!
I have a bomb!
A bomb?
You are a mad scientist.
It could be real,
he knows this stuff.
We were in chem class together.
Isn't that right, Cody?
Those were fun times.
Did you know the whole time?
We knew there were DEA kids at
school, but we didn't know who.
I saw you hanging out.
Such a weird group of friends.
It made me curious.
Then after the tunnel raid,
we wondered
if we'd made an orphan,
but I wasn't sure
until after you and I hooked up.
Good for you.
You win.
Now just let Deni go.
Look, very good!
Truck looks nice.
But why are they still alive?
- I'm gonna light this up!
-  No, you're not.
That's not a bomb.
- Look at him, he's all talk!
- Watch me!
- We are!
- Kill this mother--
Shit.
Kill him. Kill him!
Kill that bastard!
Motherfuckers!
Damn.
Over here!
Let's go!
Get down. Get down!
Go, go, go!
Let's take her. We'll trade her.
Go with your sister.
-  Benito!
- I'll meet you later.
- Look after your sister!
-  Hurry up!
Go!
Goddamnit, Cody!
Hey!
- Shit!
- Goddamn it, Ray!
Ray!
-  And Benito?
-  He's dead.
Stop!
I'm sick of you, brat!
Are you crazy or what?
Natalia, behind you!
No!
Ray, where are you?
- Down the tunnel ahead of you.
-  Deni.
No.
Dad, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!
Shut up.
Stop. Stop.
Dad, please stop!
- Shut up.
- Please stop.
Ray!
Listen. They kidnapped you
and Deni from the hospital.
They beat the shit out of you.
They brought you here. Got it?
They kidnapped you and beat
the shit out of you. Got it?
- Ray?!
- You understand? I'm sorry.
- We're good.
- Good?
Yeah. We're good. Yeah.
Deni! Are you okay?
What happened?
Um... They um...
They... They beat the shit
out of me and Deni.
Kidnapped us from the hospital
and brought us here.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, Mom, I'm okay.
I love you, Cody.
I love you, son.
I love you too, Dad. I love you.
Good?
Yeah.
He'll be okay. He's tough.
They're done, right?
- What do you mean?
- The kids, they're done...
being morons.
They fucking better be.
Come on.
Guys, let's start
with your 50-50 collar tie-up.
- Hey, Ray.
- Yep.
Got to take it easy
on the boss' kid?
No, he can take care of himself.
There it is. Nice.
Guys, change partners.
Come on, kid.
- You and me, buddy.
- All right.
This is no way to live,
Papito.
Welcome home!
- Oh my God.
-  Good to see you.
You're back. I'm so happy.
Oh, yes.
Did you bring Mexican?
- Uh... sushi.
- Sushi? Fancy.
Um, well,
welcome to our new house.
- Can I give you guys a tour?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- All right, come on.
♪ I've got blessings
rippin' out of my shoes ♪
♪ Hold my hand
I've got tricks up my sleeve ♪
♪ I'm singin' abracadabra
Little smoke in the breeze ♪
♪ Yeah, I got magic in my pocket
I've got puzzles in my head ♪
♪ Got you fallin' in love
with the slightest of hand ♪
♪ Suspend your disbelief
when I come around ♪
♪ Your pupils so dilated
I'll take a swim in your eyes ♪
♪ Your jaw keeps dropping
like I'm blowin' your mind ♪
♪ You're the impossible thing
I just keep bringing alive ♪
♪ Super calibrated so realistic
experiential rollercoaster ♪
♪ Simple things are meant
to bring you and me closer ♪
♪ Hold my hand
I've got tricks up my sleeve ♪
♪ I'm singin' abracadabra
Little smoke in the breeze ♪
♪ I've got magic in my pocket
I've got puzzles in my head ♪
♪ Got you fallin' in love
with the slightest of hand ♪
♪ It's kinda crazy though we get
to feel a feelin' like this ♪
♪ And if I play my cards right
this could end in a kiss ♪
♪ It feels like levitatin'
anytime I think of your lips ♪
♪ Skip the illusions, baby
I could get used to this ♪
♪ Hold my hand
I've got tricks up my sleeve ♪
♪ I'm singin' abracadabra
Little smoke in the breeze ♪
♪ I've got magic in my pocket
I've got puzzles in my head ♪
♪ Got you fallin' in love
with the slightest of hand ♪